♪Come closer♪
اقترب ♪
♪Be more intimate♪
♪ كن أكثر حميمية
♪Tell me if I am tempted♪
♪ قل لي إن كنت أغوى
♪The moment you and I looked at each other♪
♪ في اللحظة التي نظرت فيها أنا وأنت إلى بعضنا البعض
♪We were both tempted♪
كلانا أغوى
♪Remember how shy you were♪
♪ تذكر كم كنت خجولًا ♪
♪That day♪
♪ ذلك اليوم ♪
♪Sweet memories♪
♪ ذكريات حلوة ♪
♪Please be more♪
♪ من فضلك كن اكثر
♪How lucky I am to have you♪
♪ كم أنا محظوظ لوجودك ♪
♪So sweet♪
♪ حلوة جدا ♪
=My Naughty Assistant=
= مساعدي المشاغب =
=Episode 12=
= الحلقة 12 =
Mr. Xing.
السيد شينغ.
Duoduo took everything away.
أخذ Duoduo كل شيء بعيدًا.
Just let her go.
فقط دعها تذهب.
Well, Enchen,
حسنًا ، Enchen ،
don't be mad.
لا تغضب.
Talk to me.
تحدث معي.
That woman is like a disease.
تلك المرأة مثل المرض.
Forget her.
إنساها.
Smile.
يبتسم.
Let's go horse riding tomorrow, okay?
دعنا نذهب لركوب الخيل غدا ، حسنا؟
Cheers.
هتافات.
Well.
نحن سوف.
Enchen.
يملأ
Talk to me.
تحدث معي.
I'm here to be with you.
أنا هنا لأكون معك.
I have work to do.
لدي عمل يجب القيام به.
I'll help you.
سوف اساعدك.
Wait a moment.
انتظر لحظة.
(Maybe it is better for her to leave.)
(ربما يكون من الأفضل لها المغادرة).
Didn't you pack up your things and go?
ألم تحزم أغراضك وتذهب؟
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
You made it!
لقد فعلتها!
Amazing!
مدهش!
You like it?
هل أحببت ذلك؟
Let's go.
لنذهب.
It's not yours.
إنه ليس لك.
Aren't you leaving?
ألا تغادر؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
An act again.
فعل مرة أخرى.
I don't want be part of your play.
لا أريد أن أكون جزءًا من مسرحية.
Fooled me for so long.
خدعتني لفترة طويلة.
Am I really an idiot?
هل أنا حقا أحمق؟
Am I that gullible?
هل أنا هذا السذج؟
Right
الصحيح
now.
حاليا.
Get out of my house
اخرج من بيتي
with your stuff.
مع أشيائك.
Bye.
وداعا.
Here.
هنا.
Cheers.
هتافات.
Shall we watch a musical play after riding tomorrow?
هل نشاهد مسرحية موسيقية بعد الركوب غدا؟
I will.
أنا سوف.
And
و
you have to see my performance the day after tomorrow.
عليك أن ترى أدائي بعد غد.
What present do you like?
ما الهدية التي تحبها؟
I'll buy it for you.
سأشتريه لك.
Let me whisper.
اسمحوا لي أن أهمس.
Duoduo.
ديودو.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Don't be sad.
لا تحزن.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
I'm so sad.
انا حزين جدا.
I'm heartbroken.
انا محطم القلب.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
I'm here for you.
أنا هنا من أجلك.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
لا أعلم ما خطبتي.
I feel like I am going to choke.
أشعر أنني سأختنق.
I'll fix him.
سوف أصلحه.
Don't.
لا.
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
He's not worth it.
انه لا يستحق كل هذا العناء.
I have to take these all.
علي أن آخذ كل هؤلاء.
♪How many times in my life♪
♪ كم مرة في حياتي ♪
♪I am destined♪
أنا مقدر ♪
♪To meet you and fall in love with you♪
♪ لمقابلتك والوقوع في حبك
♪In my finest age♪
♪ في خيرة عمري ♪
♪It's a pity♪
♪ إنه لأمر مؤسف
♪That we are not together in this life♪
بأننا لسنا معًا في هذه الحياة
♪But still, thank you♪
♪ لكن مع ذلك ، شكرًا لك ♪
♪For letting me♪
♪ لسماحك لي ♪
♪Walk into your world♪
♪ امش في عالمك ♪